A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1993-1994
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1993-1994
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.962
This collection consists of 40,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1996 November 25.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by John Thomas Casteen, the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files, 1993-1994; semi-permanent records, 1931-1995; University committees files, 1982-1995; and, task forces files, 1986-1995.
Organization
SERIES I: General Files, 1993-1994 Boxes 1-56
SERIES II: Semi-Permanent Files, 1931-1995 Boxes 57-71
SERIES III: University Committees Files, 1982-1995 Box 71
SERIES IV: Task Force, 1986-1995 Boxes 72-76
SERIES V: Restricted Files, 1951-1995 Boxes 77-80
Contents List
- SERIES I: General Files
  - "A-AL"Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - "An-Az"Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--General (2 folders) (Restricted) 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Medical 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Law 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - African-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association--General and Board of Managers (1-3 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association--General and Board of Managers (4 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Anthropology 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports--President's Reports 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Architecture 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Applications for Positions (4 folders) (Restricted) 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Art--General 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Bayly Museum 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Arts Planning and Development 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Asian Studies 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Assessment Planning and Studies 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Colleges 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities (1 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities (2-4 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - Association of Western Universities 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Association Of Virginia Colleges 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Astronomy 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--General (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC) (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--College Football Association (CFA) 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) (1-2 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--NCAA (3 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - Athletics (Dan Meador's Letter) 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - Attorney General (State) 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - Auditor--Internal--General 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - "Ba-Bm" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - "Bn-Br" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - "Bs-Bz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Biology 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Birdwood--General 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance--General (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance--General Updates 1993-1994 (Box 10)
  - "Ca-Cd" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 10)
  - "Ce-Cg" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 10)
  - "Ch-Cn" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - "Coa-Com" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - "Con-Coz" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - "Cp-Cz" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Carnegie Foundation 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Carr's Hill (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - Carr's Hill/Events Summary 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - Cavalier Daily 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - Casteen, John T. III--General 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Casteen--Class--General 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Center for Innovative Technology 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Center for Public Service 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Charlottesville, City of 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Charlottesville, City of--Planning and Coordination Council 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Chemistry 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Clinch Valley College--General (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Classics 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - College Board--General (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - Commerce 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - Complaint/Request Form (Restricted) 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Community Colleges 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Comptroller (State) 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Condolences (A-Z) 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Congress 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Connie Lee 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Continuing Education--General 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Council of President 1993-1994 (Box 17)
  - "Da-De" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 17)
  - "Df-Dz" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 17)
  - "Df-Dz" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 17)
  - Darden--General 1993-1994 (Box 18)
  - Darden--General 1993-1994 (Box 18)
  - Dean's Meeting 1993-1994 (Box 18)
  - Dedications 1993-1994 (Box 18)
  - Development--General (5 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 19)
  - Drama 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - Education (1-2 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - Education (3 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 21)
  - Educational Testing Service 1993-1994 (Box 21)
  - Engineering and Applied Science (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 21)
  - English 1993-1994 (Box 21)
  - Enrollment 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Enrollment Status 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Environmental Sciences 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Equal Opportunity Office (Restricted) 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Equal Opportunity Office--General 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - "Fa-Fh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - "Fi-Fz" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - "Fi-Fz" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Management 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Faculty--General 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Family Violence Prevention Fund 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Food Services 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - French Language and Literature 1993-1994 (Box 24)
  - "Ga-Gn" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 24)
  - "Go-Gz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 24)
  - General Assembly--Legislative (4 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 25)
  - General Assembly--Legislative Summary 1993-1994 (Box 25)
  - General Assembly House Appropriations 1993-1994 (Box 25)
  - General Assembly--Senate Finance 1993-1994 (Box 25)
  - General Counsel--General 1993-1994 (Box 26)
  - General Services (State) 1993-1994 (Box 26)
  - Gifts and Grants "A-C" (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 26)
  - Gifts and Grants "D-F" (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants "G-K" (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants "L-P" (1 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 27)
  - Gifts and Grants "L-P" (2 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 28)
  - Gifts and Grants "Q-S" 1993-1994 (Box 28)
  - Gifts and Grants "T-Z" 1993-1994 (Box 28)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1993-1994 (Box 28)
  - Governor's Office--General (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Government--Commerce and Trade 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Administration 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Education 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office--Finance 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Governor's Office--Health and Human Services 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Governor's Office--Public Safety and Transportation 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Governmental Relations 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (Restricted) 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - "Ha-Hh" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - "Hi-Hz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - History 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - Honor System (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - Housing 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Department of 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - Human Resources, Key Advantage 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - Information Technology (State) 1993-1994 (Box 32)
  - Information Technology and Community (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 32)
  - International Students 1993-1994 (Box 32)
  - International Studies 1993-1994 (Box 32)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 32)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 33)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1993-1994 (Box 33)
  - Jefferson Scholars --General 1993-1994 (Box 33)
  - JRAB--General 1993-1994 (Box 33)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee 1993-1994 (Box 33)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (1 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 33)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (2-3 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 34)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 34)
  - Law--General 1993-1994 (Box 34)
  - Library--General 1993-1994 (Box 35)
  - "Ma-Me" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 35)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 35)
  - "Mf-Mz" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 36)
  - Major Events, Office of 1993-1994 (Box 36)
  - Management and Budget 1993-1994 (Box 36)
  - Mariner's Museum (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 37)
  - Material Management 1993-1994 (Box 37)
  - Mathematics 1993-1994 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center--General (1-2 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center--General (3 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 38)
  - Medical Center-- Personnel 1993-1994 (Box 38)
  - Medical Center--Health Sciences 1993-1994 (Box 38)
  - Medical Center--Hospital General 1993-1994 (Box 38)
  - Medical Center--Medical School 1993-1994 (Box 38)
  - Medical Center--Nursing (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 38)
  - Music 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - "N-Na" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - "Nb-Nz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 40)
  - NASULGC--General (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 40)
  - NASULGC--BOA 1993-1994 (Box 41)
  - NASULGC--Green Circulars 1993-1994 (Box 41)
  - National Science Foundation 1993-1994 (Box 41)
  - Nellie Mae (1-2 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 41)
  - Nellie Mae (3-4 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 42)
  - Newcomb Hall 1993-1994 (Box 42)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 42)
  - Oak Ridge Association of Universities 1993-1994 (Box 43)
  - "Pa-Ph" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 43)
  - "Pi-Pz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 44)
  - Parking and Transportation 1993-1994 (Box 44)
  - Personnel and Training (State) 1993-1994 (Box 44)
  - Physics 1993-1994 (Box 44)
  - Planning and Budget (State) 1993-1994 (Box 44)
  - Planning and Budget--University of Virginia 1993-1994 (Box 44)
  - President's Senior Cabinet Meetings (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 45)
  - Promotions and Tenure 1993-1994 (Box 45)
  - Provost--General (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 45)
  - Provost--Association Provost for Research 1993-1994 (Box 45)
  - Psychology 1993-1994 (Box 45)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 46)
  - "Ra-Rh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 46)
  - "Ri-Rz" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 46)
  - Real Estate Foundation--General 1993-1994 (Box 46)
  - Registrar 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - University of Virginia Research Association 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - ROTC--General 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - ROTC--Army 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - ROTC--Navy 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Rotunda Society 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - "Sa-Sh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - "Si-Sn" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - "So" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 48)
  - "Sp-Sz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 48)
  - Salaries--General 1993-1994 (Box 48)
  - Senate--University (1 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 48)
  - Senate--University (2 of 2) 1993-1994 (Box 49)
  - Southern Association Of Colleges and Universities (4 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 49)
  - Southern Regional Educational Board 1993-1994 (Box 50)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1993-1994 (Box 50)
  - Spanish, Italian, and Portugese 1993-1994 (Box 50)
  - SCHEV--General (1-4 of 5) 1993-1994 (Box 50)
  - SCHEV --General (5 of 5) 1993-1994 (Box 51)
  - SCHEV --Assessment 1993-1994 (Box 51)
  - SCHEV --Council Notes 1993-1994 (Box 51)
  - SCHEV --Research Note 1993-1994 (Box 51)
  - Student Affairs--General (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 51)
  - Student Affairs--Fraternities/Sororities 1993-1994 (Box 52)
  - Student Council--General 1993-1994 (Box 52)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1993-1994 (Box 52)
  - Summer Session 1993-1994 (Box 52)
  - "Ta-Te" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 52)
  - "Tf-Tz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 52)
  - Travel Invoices 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - Treasury (State) 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (1-4 of 5) 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (5 of 5) 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - United Way (Combined Certificates) 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - University Guides 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - University Journal 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - University Police 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - University Press of University of Virginia 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - University Relations/News Office 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - University Union 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (1 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 54)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (3-4 of 4) 1993-1994 (Box 55)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 55)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1993-1994 (Box 56)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1993-1994 (Box 56)
  - "Wa-Wh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 56)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 56)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 56)
- SERIES II: Semi-Permanent Files
  - Admissions--General "Permanent" (2 folders) 1972-1986 (Box 57)
  - African-American Affairs Office (2 folders) 1976-1992 (Box 57)
  - Alumni Association-- Law (3 folders) 1976-1992 (Box 58)
  - Alumni--Alumni Caucus (1-2 of 3) 1991 (Box 58)
  - Alumni--Alumni Caucus (3 of 3) 1991 (Box 59)
  - Alumni--Fraternities and Sororities (3 folders) 1988-1992 (Box 59)
  - Alumni Council of the College and Graduate School (1 of 3) 1981-1993 (Box 59)
  - Alumni Council of the College and Graduate School (2-3 of 3) 1981-1993 (Box 60)
  - American Council On Education Fellows Program II (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 60)
  - Athletics--Permanent II (2 folders) (Restricted) 1951-1992 (Box 60)
  - Athletics--Pep Band (1 of 2) 1985-1993 (Box 60)
  - Athletics--Pep Band (2 of 2) 1985-1993 (Box 61)
  - Blackburn, James (Permanent) 1993-1995 (Box 61)
  - Calloway, Dan 1993 (Box 61)
  - CAS--Visiting Committee: Art Department 1990 (Box 61)
  - Clinch Valley College: Knight, Jim A. 1988-1992 (Box 61)
  - CVC--Dean Search 1993 (Box 61)
  - Commerce--Advisory Board (2 folders) 1981-1993 (Box 61)
  - Conflict of Interest Act (Permanent)--(3 folders) 1978-1992 (Box 62)
  - Development--Developmental Procedures (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 62)
  - Economic Development--Permanent (2 folders) 1985-1993 (Box 63)
  - Faculty-Faculty Retirement (3 folders) 1988-1991 (Box 63)
  - Governmental Relations--Barnes, Dennis 1985-1992 (Box 64)
  - Governor--Dalton/Robb Virginia (Permanent) Plan-A.A. 1979-1986 (Box 64)
  - Gray, Pearl Spears (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 64)
  - Jennings, Tom 1991-1992 (Box 64)
  - Lawn Society Meeting 1992 (Box 64)
  - Minority Affairs--General (1-2 of 3) 1988-1992 (Box 64)
  - Minority Affairs--General (3 of 3) 1988-1992 (Box 65)
  - O'Neil, Robert M. 1985-1990 (Box 65)
  - Planning and Budget: Capital Outlay (2 folders) 1984-1990 (Box 65)
  - Planning and Budget (3 folders) 1990-1992 (Box 66)
  - Planning and Budget--University (2 folders) 1984-1990 (Box 66)
  - Property Records and Insurance 1973-1988 (Box 67)
  - Provost--Jackson, Thomas H. 1991-1994 (Box 67)
  - Provost--Kelly, Hugh P. 1931-1992 (Box 67)
  - Change and Improvement in Virginia Education (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 67)
  - SCHEV--Change and Improvement In Education (2 folders) 1992 (Box 67)
  - Virginians For Progress Foundation (Support) (4 folders) 1992 (Box 68)
  - Visitors--General (1 of 2) 05-09,1993 (Box 68)
  - Visitors--General (2 of 2) 05-09, 1993 (Box 69)
  - Visitors--General (2 folders) 01-04, 1993 (Box 69)
  - Visitors--General (2 folders) 01-12, 1992 (Box 69)
  - Visitors--Academic Enhancement Program (I) (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 70)
  - Visitors--Special Committee Clinch Valley College 1992 (Box 70)
  - Visitors--Special Committee: Presidential Selection Process Study 1990 (Box 70)
  - Visitors--Special Committee: Search for a President 1989-1990 (Box 70)
  - Visitors--Ballenger, J. Scott (Student) 1992 (Box 70)
  - Horsley, Waller H. (1 of 2) 1982-1993 (Box 70)
  - Horsley, Waller H. (2 of 2) 1982-1993 (Box 71)
  - Nicholas, Freddie W., Sr. 1990-1993 (Box 71)
  - Vice Presidential Committees 1992-1993 (Box 71)
- SERIES III: University Committees
  - University Committee--General 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Arboretum and Landscape 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Athletics Advisory Council 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Benefits 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Calendar 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Commemoration of the 100th Anniversary Rotunda Fire 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Commencement and Convocations 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Commencements and Convocations, Subcommittee Public Occasions 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Financial Aid 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Information Technology and Communication 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Interests of Persons w/ Disabilities 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee-- Libraries 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Master Planning Council 1994 (Box 71)
  - University Committee-- Names 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Radiation Safety 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Residential Life 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Security and General Safety 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Sexual Assault and Judicial Policy 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Thomas Jefferson Award 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Traffic Appeals 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Transportation and Parking 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Undergraduate Admissions 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Univ Press of Virginia 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Virginia Quarterly Review 1994-1995 (Box 71)
  - University Committee--Virginia Status of University Students (Restricted) 1994-1995 (Box 71)
- SERIES IV: Task Force
  - University Committee--Women's Concerns 1994-1995 (Box 72)
  - Task Force--African-American Affairs (3 folders) 1989-1994 (Box 72)
  - Task Force--African-American Affairs (1 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 72)
  - Task Force--African-American Affairs (2 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 73)
  - Task Force--African-American Affairs (2 folders) 1988 Jan (Box 73)
  - Task Force--African-American Affairs (1 of 2) 1986-1987 (Box 73)
  - Task Force--African-American Affairs (2 of 2) 1986-1987 (Box 74)
  - Task Force--Council on Community (2 folders) 1992 (Box 74)
  - Task Force on Status of Women (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 74)
  - Task Force Status of Women (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 75)
  - Task Force: Status of Women 1987 (Box 75)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Graduate Arts and Sciences Deanship Search (Restricted) 1988-1990 (Box 75)
  - Steering Committee: Salary Equity Study 1991 (Box 75)
  - Advisory Committee: Vice-President for Development and University Relations 1989-1991 (Box 75)
  - Search (1 of 2)
  - Advisory Committee: Vice-President for Development and University Relations Search (2 of 2) 1989-1991 (Box 76)
  - Vice-President for Development Search 1991 (Box 76)
  - Search for Vice-President and Provost (Ad Hoc Comm) (2 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 76)
- SERIES V: Restricted Materials (Box Boxes 77-80)